

# Ilya Zaitsev **Frontend Engineer**

Contacts

**Email** godested@gmail.com



Phone

+380 63 400 6684



Website

godested.me

Location



Kyiv, Ukraine

Socials

LinkedIn godested



@\_godested



Instagram @ztsvi



@godested

Languages



English Upper-Intermediate



Ukrainian/Russian

# Professional summary

Enthusiastic front-end engineer with more than 5 years of commercial experience. Good at project development from scratch and improvement of existing solutions. Have analytical and investigative skills. I confidently understand how to build an MVP. Able to create full autonomy in front-end development. Strive to improve DX and automate code quality analysis. Familiar with unit economics. Ready to analyze business requirements and propose product and development flow improvements

I strive to find a professional environment to implement knowledge and gained experience, be a part of the "Big idea" project and improve management skills.

# Experience



Playtech · Live

Senior Frontend Engineer

Sep 2020 - Present · 1 yr 9 mos Kyiv, Ukraine

I played a significant part in developing 5 new games for tens of thousands of users, was engaged in code reviews, improving DX, refactoring existing solutions, and developing new complex features.

TypeScript, React, Mobx, RxJS, Inversify, Webpack, Protobuf, Jest, Kibana, Jenkins.



Genesis

Senior Frontend Engineer

May 2019 - Sep 2020 · 1 yr 5 mos Kyiv, Ukraine

The successfully launched social app and brand landings with further evolution to a full-fledged product (support, analytics, payments). Various projects have used me as an interviewer for hiring senior developers.

React, Redux, Redux-Saga, Webpack, Gatsby, TypeScript, GitLab CI/CD, Docker, Sentry, PRPL pattern.



#### Skywell Software

Frontend Developer

Nov 2018 - Mar 2019 · 5 mos Kyiv, Ukraine

In cooperation with a back-end developer, based on UX mockups, successfully developed an application with a graphical representation of business processes in a BPMN and CMMN formats for immediate execution.

React, Redux, Redux-Saga, Webpack, CMMN, BPMN, Docker.



Lab73

Frontend Developer

May 2018 - Nov 2018 · 7 mos Kyiv, Ukraine

Mobile-first, cross-browser, and SEO-friendly app for finding the closest money exchangers with a favorable rate was developed from scratch. Developed service for medical members with real-time calls, pptx presentations, and schedule manager.

React, Redux, Redux-Saga, Webpack, Mapbox, WebSockets, WebRTC, Docker.



WorkRocks

Frontend Developer

Feb 2018 - May 2018 · 3 mos Dnipro, Ukraine

Participated in the development of a real-time crypto-currencies exchanger.

React, Redux, TypeScript, WebSockets, Node.js.



Upwork

Frontend Developer

Mar 2017 - May 2018 · 1 yr 3 mos Dnipro, Ukraine

Under the supervision of a mentor, was developed a banking system and a lot of landing pages. React, Redux, WebSockets, Gulp, Node.js, Ruby.

### Education



Frontend Pro

Oct 2017 - Jan 2018 Course certificate



Frontend Basic Aug 2017 - Oct 2017

Course certificate



Computer Engineering Sep 2017

# Highlights

I'm familiar with fast prototyping and release MVP for early test ideas in the real world. It took me about 3 months to analyze requirements, set up the development flow, and create the first social discovery MVP (with paying customers) version of the latest released project.

I've hacked a game dedicated to the contest at OdessaJS while sitting at the OdessaJS conference 😄

